natgeotv.co.in 2015-12-24

# PRIVACY POLICY - National Geographic Channel - India

1\. **Information** \- When using the Website You may be asked to enter Information. The Information will only be used for the purposes explained when you have been asked to enter the Information and/or in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

2\. **Provision of Information to Third Parties** \- We will not sell or otherwise transfer the Information to unaffiliated third parties without Your approval. If applicable, You will have the opportunity to indicate whether You would like to "opt in" to receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from Us and/or any third parties.

3\. **Analysis of User Behaviour** \- We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of user behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Website and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties who request personal information and You should check the applicable privacy policy of that party.

4\. **Cookies** \- You should be aware that information and data may be automatically collected through the use of "cookies". "Cookies" are small text files a website can use to recognise repeat users and allow Us to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve the Website and to target its advertising. Cookies do not attach to Your system and damage Your files. If You do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows You to deny or accept the cookie feature.

5\. **Updating or Removing Information** \- You may notify Us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected Information by using the Feedback Form on the Website. Further, upon Your request, We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete Your Information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete a Your entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions.

6\. **Changes to this Policy** \- We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this privacy policy and any changes shall be notified to You.

7\. **Transfer of Information** \- The Information may be transferred by us to our computer servers in other countries given the global nature of our business. Any transfer of information is in accordance with the UK and EU law on Data Protection. Currently those servers are located in India and the United States of America.
